Thirteen at Dinner is a crime, mystery film directed by Lou Antonio.
Actress Jane Wilkinson wants a divorce, but her husband, Lord Edgware, refuses.
She convinces Hercule Poirot to use his famed tact and logic to make her case.
Lord Edgware turns up murdered, a well-placed
knife wound at the base of his neck.
It will take the precise Poirot to sort out the lies from the alibis
- and find the criminal before another victim dies.
Hercule Poirot, played by Peter Ustinov.
Jane Wilkinson / Charlotta Adams, played by Faye Dunaway.
Capt. Arthur Hastings, played by Jonathan Cecil.
Ronald Marsh, played by Bill Nighy.
Jenny Driver, played by Diane Keen.
Film Director, played by John Stride.
Thirteen at Dinner is a 1985 British-American made-for-television
mystery film featuring the Belgian detective Hercule Poirot.
Adapted by Rod Browning from the 1933 Agatha Christie novel Lord Edgware Dies, it was directed by Lou Antonio and starred Peter Ustinov, Faye Dunaway, Jonathan
Cecil, Diane Keen, Bill Nighy and David Suchet, who was later to play Poirot in the long-running television series entitled Agatha Christie's Poirot.
The film first aired on CBS Television on October 18, 1985.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, detective, murder mystery.
The tone is mind_bending.